http://www.zaring.com/privacy/

For the best experience, please use one of the following Browsers: IE10+, Chrome, Firefox, or Safari.
Skip to main content
Skip to footer content
PRIVACY POLICY
This Privacy Policy ("Policy"), effective December 29, 2014, tells you about The Drees Company's privacy practices governing personal information we may collect when you visit our website, and how we may use and share that information. Your prior activities on the site may have been governed by an earlier version of this Policy.
From time to time, we may use your information for new, unanticipated uses not previously disclosed in our Policy. If our information practices do change materially, we will post the changes to our website and revise our Policy accordingly. In addition, if we have collected personally-identifying information from you, we will notify you and secure your consent before using your personal information in new ways.
What Information Do We Collect?
Personal Information:
We collect personal and contact information you choose to provide to us in connection with your activities on the site.
If you choose to register on the site, we collect your name, email, postal address, and other information such as your home preferences, moving plans, payment calculations, questions/comments, and the like. You may also register to save your favorites across devices.
If you leave a customer service request, we collect your community and job number.
If you participate in promotions such as contests or sweepstakes via the site, we will collect name and contact information from you when you enter.
If you use the "Get Directions" feature of the site, we will collect your current location.
Other user information we collect:
In addition, for each visitor to our site, we automatically gather certain other potentially identifying information and store it in log files. This information includes (as applicable) internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, your operating system, date/time stamp, processor or device serial number, unique device identifier, and clickstream data. We collect and store this information on an individual basis and in aggregate, or combined, form. We also collect both user-specific and aggregate information on what pages visitors access or visit.
"Do Not Track" Signals. We do not currently have the capability to recognize browser "Do Not Track" signals. We adhere to the standards set forth in this privacy policy.
Cookies. A cookie is a small text file that is stored on a user's computer for record-keeping purposes. If you reject cookies, you may still use our site, but your ability to use some areas of our site will be limited. We use session cookies to make it easier for you to navigate our site. We use session cookies to record session information, such as which web pages a user has visited, and to track user activity on the site. We also use session cookies to store any passwords used on the site (such as a password associated with a user account), so you don't have to enter it more than once per session. Session cookies expire when you close your browser. Analytics. To determine how many users visit our site, how often they visit this site, and to better understand the areas of greatest interest to our visitors, we use tools called "Google Analytics" and "Eloqua" (a subsidiary of Oracle) to compile this information for us. As a result of your visit to our site, these companies may collect information such as your domain type, your IP address and clickstream information. We do not combine the information collected through the use of analytics tools with personally identifiable information. For more information about the analytics companies' ability to use and share information about your visits to this site, see http://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/ and http://www.envisiondesignonline.com/privacy-policy/  and https://www.salesforce.com/company/privacy/.
Ad Networks. As you browse our site, advertising cookies will be placed on your computer to help us understand what products and services you are interested in. When you visit other sites, our display advertising partners let us show you retargeting advertising based on your interaction with our site. Our ad partners do not collect personal information such as your name, email address, postal address, or telephone number.
How Do We Use and Share the Information We Collect?
We store and process your personal information to provide our services, to personalize your experience on the site, and to contact you with messages we think might interest you (such as newsletters and promotional emails).
We use information we collect to analyze trends, to administer the site, and to track users' movements around the site. We also use this information to improve the content of our web pages and to make our site more useful to visitors.
None of the personal information you provide to us through the site is displayed publicly. We do not share personal information we collect with any third parties, except to the extent reasonably necessary to comply with law enforcement requests and judicial proceedings, to ensure the safety and security of the site, and to engage others to assist us in serving you (for example, conducting surveys or market research on our behalf).
It is possible that, at some time in the future, our company may be sold along with its assets, or may engage in business transactions in which customer information is one of the assets transferred. In such a case, the customer information which we have gathered may be one of the business assets we transfer.
How Long Do We Keep the Information We Collect?
We will retain your personal information in accordance with our continuing business need to service this relationship and/or to improve our site services.
Security
The security of your personal information is important to us. We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, and to guard that information against loss, misuse, or alteration.
Please note, however, that no method of transmission over the internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure. Therefore, while we use commercially-reasonable means to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.
Links to Third Party Sites
This Policy applies only to information collected by this website. From time to time, this website may link you to other sites ("Linked Sites") that are not owned by us. We do not control the collection or use of any information, including personal information, that occurs during your visit to the Linked Sites. Further, we make no representations about the privacy policies or practices of the Linked Sites, and we are not responsible for their privacy practices. Be careful of disclosing any of your personally identifiable information when leaving our site. We encourage you to be aware when you leave our site and to read the privacy statements of every website that collects personally identifiable information.
Questions About Our Privacy Policy and Practices
If you have any questions about the Policy or our privacy practices, you may contact:
The Drees Company 211 Grandview Drive Fort Mitchell, Kentucky 41017 859-578-4200 dreeswebmaster@dreeshomes.com
May We Help You?
›
×
Close
×
Close
Close
×
Close
Close
×
Close
Search Results:
Previous
Next
×
Close
Google Map
Drees Directions and Hours
Get Directions
Drees Driving Directions and Hours
%
Yearly Property Tax (optional)
$
Yearly Property Insurance (optional)
$
*This calculator is made available to you as a self-help tool for your independent use. We cannot and do not guarantee its accuracy or its applicability to your circumstances. We encourage you to seek personalized advice from qualified professionals regarding all personal finance issues.
Save
Thank you for your interest in a Drees home.
We will be contacting you shortly regarding your inquiry.
Thank you for your interest in a Drees Home.
Unfortunately, there was a problem submitting your request. Please try again.
Regional selection allows our system to serve the correct data around the focus of your needs.
Select A Region
Austin
Cincinnati/Northern Kentucky
Cleveland/Northeast Ohio
Dallas-Ft Worth
Houston
Indianapolis
Jacksonville
Nashville
Raleigh/Durham
Washington D.C./Virginia/Maryland
I'm here to make your search for the ideal Drees home quick and easy. I can answer your questions about schools, drive times, taxes, financing, and much more.
I can also schedule an appointment for you to tour a home and meet with one of our Market Managers either in person or virtually! Please complete the form and I'll talk to you soon.
Thank you for considering Drees Homes!
Yes, I would like to receive email regarding Drees’ current promotions, home designs, and other related topics.
›Submit
Thank you for your submission, I will be contacting you shortly.
To better serve you can you please provide any additional information about your request.
Please select the type of home you would like more information about:
Please send me an information packet by postal mail (mailing address needed above).
‹
Back
»
Submit
×
Close
Please Choose Your Location
Select...
Select...
×
Close
Please Choose Your Location
Select...
Select...
Lorem ipsum dolor sit amet, consectetur adipisicing elit, sed do eiusmod
tempor incididunt ut labore et dolore magna aliqua. Ut enim ad minim veniam,
quis nostrud exercitation ullamco laboris nisi ut aliquip ex ea commodo
consequat.
Select...
